Here I come, Koon.
Bring it!
Koon!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay, guys.
Really!
Yeah, right!
I used Koo to guard my arms and head,
but my legs just couldn't brace hard enough.
But next time,
I'm gonna catch it for sure!
Koon!
You can fly again, you can fly away, the world is your輝き.
大地を踏みしめて君は目覚めてゆく 天使の微笑みで連れ出して
始まりはいつでも遅くないさ 何度でも立ち上がれ
次回予告
this is it no you're fine okay I'm better now hey just so you know I'm the type to hold a grudge
it's time for payback razor the black one switches with others damn you really got me good that's what
you get you mess with me and I'll take you out razor will use back to return to play anyway at least we
made him use it up early plus it'll be our ball what in the hell now that's one interesting ability
nurture it well okay hold on just a second what the heck was that there's no rule against passing
the ball to an opponent and as you've probably noticed you're welcome to hit people in the face
here that means that his attack was also legal if the ball had actually touched the floor I'd be out
now once he's unconscious the nen beast disappears his ability requires his direct control the black
gorilla may begin inside the court but that's assuming Gorenu ever regains consciousness which
something tells me isn't likely if the in court players are reduced to zero before Gorenu wakes up
the match will be over there's no way he's out cold he might wake up he might even wake up before we lose
but in the condition that he's in he won't be able to conjure his nin beast inside the court it's three on
three but we're seriously outmatched that's obvious half our players are gone and we've only got one hurt kid
on the outside our opponents have a solid outside team so they can attack from anywhere razor still inside
without having to use back and the ball rebounded to our opponents or at a clear disadvantage all right
well tell me who wants to be next me what do I do I can't catch it I've got a dodge
it turned on a dime
bungee gum
the bastard can't believe it he faked going for me but his real goal was taking out both
biscuit and hisoka wait a minute what if he was gambling that I dodged to the left instead
if I'd done that
biscuit is out
step out of the court what happened didn't she dodge
i'm out what
so that means that clothing counts as part of your body yes
i was almost positive she dodged it we're down to two no matter what don't let them get the ball
back
gone has used back and may now return to the court
are you sure we can trust the little kid with this that one's no ordinary little kid
he's the only one of us who's even tried to catch razors throw
are you all right yeah now listen to me carefully do not overdo it yeah
what's one plus one yeah it's hopeless okay then beat him even if it kills you
boss
you all good
yup
i learned something rather interesting
if the ball travels outside the court it becomes much less powerful
i only broke two fingers without ko so as long as we can avoid razors attacks we might just be okay
my thoughts exactly but what kind of victory is that
look don't be an idiot if we can't win no matter what we do all of this is pointless you better calm
down you're being stupid i thought you'd be mad you what if you dodge left then you could have been killed
it's true
i'm really pissed off right now and i'm not gonna settle for some cheap win
i have to completely crush this guy
in that case you must have some kind of plan in mind yeah
i've got this kilua stand over there
bend your knees and hold the ball tight sure
i get it
now show me rock
his aura just spiked
john
ken
his aura just spiked
i got
john
yeah
Number 13 is out.
Catching the ball while your body is touching outside the court is illegal.
Possession goes to Team Gon.
Did you guys see that?
He just sent the biggest one of them flying!
Damn it! That one wasn't nearly good enough!
Why does he look so unhappy? You're right, he looks mad.
That kid has got real high standards.
Not yet.
That's not enough to beat the real Razor.
I need a lot more power!
You ready? Let's do it again!
Hit Razor with everything you've got!
I'm going to need a whole lot more power if I'm going to bring down Razor!
Look!
Wren!
His aura so immense.
I think you picked the wrong sport.
Nothing in the rules limits the amount of time he can take to build up his power.
Might want to get out of the way.
You're kidding, right?
Take all the built-up aura and focus it into my fist!
Okay, show me rock!
Take this, Razor!
John!
Ken!
Roar!
Perfect! You'll never catch that!
He's bumping it?
He used his own body to slow its momentum.
He's good. His timing had to be flawless and he deflected the force so smoothly.
This man is really strong.
That was great!
The game's not all about dodging and catching, but that advice is a bit too little too late I'm afraid.
I don't get it! That ball was as strong as his, but it... it didn't even reach the ceiling!
That was one hell of a bump to burn off all that momentum. Now it's right above him!
Bungie gum!
Oh, that's too bad. You're actually supposed to catch it, you know.
As per the cushion rule, Razor is out! Step outside!
I call back!
Razor has used back! He will remain inside the court and play will resume!
Both teams have used back and it's three on two! Yeah! Looks like the table's a turn!
You really think so?
From where I'm sitting, our team is the one on the ropes.
Hisoka probably isn't in any shape to throw. I'd be surprised if he could even hold the ball with his right hand.
Goen's attacks use a huge amount of aura. That takes its toll. He should feel completely drained right about now.
Can he muster another attack that powerful? It's highly unlikely.
That means... Kilo is the only uninjured one inside?
Quite the opposite.
I would venture that of the three, he's probably the most gravely injured.
What do you mean?
Are you doing okay there, Goen?
Yeah. But I think the next one will be the last. So I'll give it everything I've got.
Alright. Just make it good.
One more. I can take it. I've just gotta hold out.
When Goen struck the ball, I noticed that Killua barely used any protective Nen on his hands.
That's crazy! That launch was intense! He was like a damn cannon!
Correct. And essentially, Killua used his bare hands to form that cannon's barrel.
But with the right amount of Nen, if he'd used just enough to protect them,
his aura would have become a barrier against Goen's punch, significantly reducing the amount of power to the ball.
In order to keep himself from weakening the ball's velocity, Killua used hardly any aura on his hands, sacrificing them in the process.
That tells me that as bad as Hisoka's right hand might be at the moment, Killua's hands must be in much worse condition.
Damn. I feel like such a fool. Why am I not up there with them?
I know the technique, and I can do it much faster than Killua.
Killua. In the moment before Goen touches the ball, I could swiftly switch my aura to my hands. A near instant transfer.
Wait!
Time out. Hey ref, question.
Yes? What is it?
I was just wondering if the players inside of the court can choose to move to the outside.
Well, that doesn't violate any rules, but be aware that you can't return inside.
Alright. Come here!
Goen, if you just step outside of the court before you strike, I can hold the ball for you.
Killua's hands must be totally ravaged by now. I sincerely doubt that he's in any condition to hold the ball or anything else.
I know a way that'll allow me to protect my hands with a lightning-fast coating of aura.
I can hold the ball while you take out Razor from here. It's the only way that we can win this.
We can't do that.
But why not? What's the problem with that?
It feels like a cop-out.
You're kidding! This is not the time to be thinking like that!
Hey, don't overdo it, old man. You took a hit. You're only gonna make it feel worse.
I'm doing fine. I'm not hurt nearly as bad as you might think.
Okay, then. Show me your hands.
I said I'm fine.
Ugh.
Like I thought. I'll bet you we can't feel anything but pain.
I can do this! I can take one more, okay?
Goen, I know I can do it!
Impossible! I'm right. Please help me convince him.
I... I already knew that Killua's hands were hurt.
I'm sorry, Mr. Tezgera, but I won't move out of the court.
I need him to hold the ball for me!
I can't do this without Killua!
If Fiskit or Hisuka held it, I probably couldn't use my full strength.
There's only one reason I can focus everything I've got on hitting the ball.
It's because I know Killua's the one holding it!
There it is, old man. Do you get it now? Why don't you go get some rest?
I understand.
Good luck.
The ball. Give it here, Hisuka.
We will now resume the match.
Now, to be perfectly honest, I'm not very good at throwing!
Looks to me like we're even.
Brilliant! The way she hit him is rebounding the ball to us!
Number two is out!
And that means we're down to...
Razor himself!
Gone. First, we need to get the ball back from Razor.
No sweat!
One sec.
I see. Sounds like fun.
Yeah. I'm just not convinced it's gonna work.
Maybe not. But I'd certainly love to try either way.
Let's give it a shot, Killua!
Okay.
I believe that settles it.
Man, you always come up with the craziest ideas, don't you?
I'm counting on you!
We will now resume the match!
Gone and Killua share a powerful bond of mutual trust.
Their friendship is strong.
But when Hisoka is added to the equation,
there's no telling what sort of secret play will emerge.
The players will call us.
And yet the play will emerge.
What kind ofidethe plans will come for her?
The money goes for the rusharas J
Thank you.
Coming up, the Great Island Tutorial!